

## **ABOUT ME**

My name is Nilay. I'm 24 years old. I graduated from Web Design and Coding department with an associate degree from Anadolu University and I graduated from Computer Engineering department with an Bachelor's degree from University of Selcuk. I'm studying master's degree from University of Konya Technical. I did my first internship and second internship at Innova of Telco OSS/BSS department. I worked Desmer Güvenlik Hizmetleri Tic. A.Ş of IT departmant. I am working Smart Maple Software. I am interested in data analysis and Java projects. I'm dealing with Java projects and artificial intelligence projects. I also develop myself in web technologies. I like to do research and I like to manage projects.

# CONTACT

- İstasyon Mah. Alan Sok. No:13/5 Bağlıca/Etimesgut/ANKARA
- nilaycezik@gmail.com
- 0505 856 6930
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/nilaycezik/
- 1 https://github.com/Nilaycezik
- https://nilaycezik.github.io/

## SKILLS

- Web Programming Languages(HTML5, CSS3JavaScript)
- \*Spring/SpringBoot
- \*Java Programming Language
- \*MS SOL Database
- \* Web Scrapping & Selenium
- Kaggle
- Python Programming Language
- Data Preprocessing
- Data Mining
- TensorFlow & Keras Library
- Figma
- Aws cloud console

## **EXPERIENCE**

# SMART MAPLE WEB & DATA SOLUTIONS 08.2021-Now

Web Scrapping and Python Developer

## DESMER GÜVENLİK HİZMETLERİA.Ş. 11.2020-08.2021

Information Technologies Assistant Specialist

# İNNOVA BİLİŞİMÇÖZÜMLERİ A.Ş. — 2. Intership 07.2019 - 09.2019

Intelligent Talent – The purpose of this project, which I prepared as the second internship project, is to design a modern-day WEB site using Rest architecture and using SpringBoot technology prepared in accordance with MVC and H2 embedded database.

## İNNOVA BİLİŞİMÇÖZÜMLERİ A.Ş. — 1. Intership 07.2018 - 09.2018

Remember Your Friend- The purpose of this project, which I prepared as my first internship project, is to design a console application developed on the Java platform that can send mail as a birthday reminder.



## **EDUCATION**

University of Konya Technical – Computer Engineering – Master's Degree

– Now– GPA: 3,60 –Konya, Turkey

University of Selcuk— Computer Engineering — Bachelor's Degree —GPA: 2,88 — Konya, Turkey

University of Anadolu— Web Design and Coding — Associate Degree — GPA: 2,14— Eskisehir, Turkey

Hazım Kulak Anatolium High School – Aksaray, Turkey

# LANGUAGES

English – Intermadiate Germany - Elementary

## **COURSES & CERTIFICATES**

### Sıfırdan İleri Seviyeye Komple Java Geliştirici Kursu

Udemy|2018

Certificate of Competence:

https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-VOAM34Y9.pdf

#### A'danZ'yeBootstrap4

111------2021

Certificate of Competence:

https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-326cb8b1- e60b-43ad-a1e4- 3b84861104b2.pdf

#### Algoritma ve Programlama Mantığı Eğitimi

Udemy|2021

Certificate of Competence:

https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-5dc344c1-3f29-4f1a-b2ed-596524c2e246.pdf

## Baştan Sona C Programlama Eğitimi

Udemy|2021

Certificate of Competence:

https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-5f922d22-30ba-4e6b-9f99- 3bfa92f8a5bf.pdf

#### Bir Saatte CSSÖğren

Udemy|2021

Certificate of Competence:

 $\underline{https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-b336176b-\ 9d88-4d8b-85a4-\ 6e999aba0c99.pdf}$ 

#### Bir Saatte HTML Öğren

Udemy|2021

Certificate of Competence:

https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-15da5cc9-81bf-440a-b65f- 0efbe2a8fed3.pdf

### Web Tasarımı ve Kodlama+ SEO

Udemy|2021

Certificate of Competence:

 $\frac{https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-f2c78bd8-e20d-4a66-8b98-\ 1eab5444415d.pdf}{}$ 

#### Web Yazılımına Giriş HTML CSS JavaScript Temel Eğitim

Udemy|2021

Certificate of Competence:

 $\frac{https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-80351492-7f24-461f-93a2-9be13de89f92.pdf}{}$